https://lagois.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Lagois Drafting and Construction respects your right to privacy and is committed to protecting that right.
Any personal information you provide to us, including your name, address, telephone number and email address, will not be released, sold or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Lagois. While we do our best to protect your personal information you transmit to us, and you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information.
Lagois is not responsible for the content of external Internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites and to contact them directly if you have any questions about their privacy policy, before disclosing any personal information.
This website contains Google Analytics Advertising features. It is our responsibility to notify our visitors by disclosing the following information in our privacy policy:
The Google Analytics Advertising Features have been implemented.
Our third-party vendors and this website uses first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) or other first-party identifiers, and third-party cookies (such as Google advertising cookies) or other third-party identifiers together.
Visitors can opt-out of the Google Analytics Advertising Features you use, including through Ads Settings, Ad Settings for mobile apps, or any other available means (for example, the NAI’s consumer opt-out).
We also encourage you to point users to Google Analytics’ currently available opt-outs for the web.
Lagois is belongs to an association of Professional Technologists, Tarion, Renomark, CHBA, OHBA, GOHBA.
